[
    {
        "front": "之",
        "back": "marks preceding phrase as modifier of following phrase; it, him her, them; go to",
        "pronunciation": "zhī",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "部",
        "back": "part, division, section",
        "pronunciation": "bù",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "无",
        "back": "negative, no, not; KangXi radical 71",
        "pronunciation": "wú",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "与",
        "back": "and; with; to; for; give, grant",
        "pronunciation": "yǔ",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "民",
        "back": "people, subjects, citizens",
        "pronunciation": "mín",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "此",
        "back": "this, these; in this case, then",
        "pronunciation": "cǐ",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "使",
        "back": "cause, send on a mission, order; envoy, messenger, ambassador",
        "pronunciation": "shǐ",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "性",
        "back": "nature, character, sex",
        "pronunciation": "xìng",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "全",
        "back": "maintain, keep whole or intact",
        "pronunciation": "quán",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "将",
        "back": "will, going to, future; general",
        "pronunciation": "jiāng",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "由",
        "back": "cause, reason; from",
        "pronunciation": "yóu",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "并",
        "back": "",
        "pronunciation": "bìng",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "美",
        "back": "beautiful, pretty; pleasing",
        "pronunciation": "měi",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "利",
        "back": "gains, advantage, profit, merit",
        "pronunciation": "lì",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "合",
        "back": "combine, unite, join; gather",
        "pronunciation": "hé",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "内",
        "back": "inside",
        "pronunciation": "nèi",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "度",
        "back": "degree, system; manner; to consider",
        "pronunciation": "dù",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "任",
        "back": "trust to, rely on, appoint; to bear, duty, office; allow",
        "pronunciation": "rèn",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "海",
        "back": "sea, ocean; maritime",
        "pronunciation": "hǎi",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "通",
        "back": "pass through, common, communicate",
        "pronunciation": "tōng",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "原",
        "back": "source, origin, beginning",
        "pronunciation": "yuán",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "及",
        "back": "extend; reach; come up to; and",
        "pronunciation": "jí",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "论",
        "back": "debate; discuss; discourse",
        "pronunciation": "lùn",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "处",
        "back": "place, locale; department",
        "pronunciation": "chù",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "各",
        "back": "each, individually, every, all",
        "pronunciation": "gè",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "入",
        "back": "enter, come in(to), join",
        "pronunciation": "rù",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "活",
        "back": "live, exist, survive; lively",
        "pronunciation": "huó",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "尔",
        "back": "you; that, those; final particle",
        "pronunciation": "ěr",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "何",
        "back": "what, why, where, which, how",
        "pronunciation": "hé",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "反",
        "back": "reverse, opposite, contrary, anti",
        "pronunciation": "fǎn",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "受",
        "back": "receive, accept, get; bear, stand",
        "pronunciation": "shòu",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "量",
        "back": "measure, quantity, capacity",
        "pronunciation": "liàng",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "建",
        "back": "build, establish, erect, found",
        "pronunciation": "jiàn",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "计",
        "back": "plan, plot; strategem; scheme",
        "pronunciation": "jì",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "管",
        "back": "pipe, tube, duct; woodwind music",
        "pronunciation": "guǎn",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "资",
        "back": "property; wealth; capital",
        "pronunciation": "zī",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "命",
        "back": "life; destiny, fate, luck; an order, instruction",
        "pronunciation": "mìng",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "金",
        "back": "gold; metals in general; money",
        "pronunciation": "jīn",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "指",
        "back": "finger, toe; point, indicate",
        "pronunciation": "zhǐ",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "克",
        "back": "gram; overcome; transliteration",
        "pronunciation": "kè",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "许",
        "back": "allow, permit; promise; betroth",
        "pronunciation": "xǔ",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "区",
        "back": "area, district, region, ward",
        "pronunciation": "qū",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "保",
        "back": "protect, safeguard, defend, care",
        "pronunciation": "bǎo",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "至",
        "back": "reach, arrive; extremely, very",
        "pronunciation": "zhì",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "队",
        "back": "team, group; army unit",
        "pronunciation": "duì",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "社",
        "back": "god of the soil and altars to him; group of families; company, society",
        "pronunciation": "shè",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "展",
        "back": "open, unfold; stretch, extend",
        "pronunciation": "zhǎn",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "科",
        "back": "section, department, science",
        "pronunciation": "kē",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "基",
        "back": "foundation, base",
        "pronunciation": "jī",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "则",
        "back": "rule, law, regulation; grades",
        "pronunciation": "zé",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "却",
        "back": "still, but; decline; retreat",
        "pronunciation": "què",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "光",
        "back": "light, brilliant, shine; only",
        "pronunciation": "guāng",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "即",
        "back": "promptly, quickly, immediately",
        "pronunciation": "jí",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "象",
        "back": "elephant; ivory; figure, image",
        "pronunciation": "xiàng",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "式",
        "back": "style, system, formula, rule",
        "pronunciation": "shì",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "程",
        "back": "journey, trip; schedule, agenda",
        "pronunciation": "chéng",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "死",
        "back": "die; dead; death",
        "pronunciation": "sǐ",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "交",
        "back": "mix; intersect; exchange, communicate; deliver",
        "pronunciation": "jiāo",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "规",
        "back": "rules, regulations, customs, law",
        "pronunciation": "guī",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "取",
        "back": "take, receive, obtain; select",
        "pronunciation": "qǔ",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "拉",
        "back": "pull, drag; seize, hold; lengthen",
        "pronunciation": "lā",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "格",
        "back": "pattern, standard, form; style",
        "pronunciation": "gé",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "术",
        "back": "art, skill, special feat; method, technique",
        "pronunciation": "shù",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "确",
        "back": "sure, certain; real, true",
        "pronunciation": "què",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "传",
        "back": "summon; propagate, transmit",
        "pronunciation": "chuán",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "观",
        "back": "see, observe, view; appearance",
        "pronunciation": "guān",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "切",
        "back": "cut, mince, slice, carve",
        "pronunciation": "qiè",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "导",
        "back": "direct, guide, lead, conduct",
        "pronunciation": "dǎo",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "争",
        "back": "dispute, fight, contend, strive",
        "pronunciation": "zhēng",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "改",
        "back": "change, alter; improve, remodel",
        "pronunciation": "gǎi",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "收",
        "back": "gather together, collect; harvest",
        "pronunciation": "shōu",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "言",
        "back": "words, speech; speak, say",
        "pronunciation": "yán",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "联",
        "back": "connect, join; associate, ally",
        "pronunciation": "lián",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "持",
        "back": "sustain, support; hold, grasp",
        "pronunciation": "chí",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "济",
        "back": "help, aid, relieve; ferry, cross",
        "pronunciation": "jì",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "亲",
        "back": "relatives, parents; intimate the hazel nut or filbert tree a thorny tree",
        "pronunciation": "qīn",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "林",
        "back": "forest, grove; surname",
        "pronunciation": "lín",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "士",
        "back": "scholar, gentleman; soldier",
        "pronunciation": "shì",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "证",
        "back": "prove, confirm, verify; proof",
        "pronunciation": "zhèng",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "失",
        "back": "lose; make mistake, neglect",
        "pronunciation": "shī",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "转",
        "back": "shift, move, turn",
        "pronunciation": "zhuǎn",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "存",
        "back": "exist, live, be; survive; remain",
        "pronunciation": "cún",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "台",
        "back": "platform; unit; term of address",
        "pronunciation": "tái",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "具",
        "back": "tool, implement; draw up, write",
        "pronunciation": "jù",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "流",
        "back": "flow, circulate, drift; class",
        "pronunciation": "liú",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "连",
        "back": "join, connect; continuous; even",
        "pronunciation": "lián",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "深",
        "back": "deep; depth; far; very, extreme",
        "pronunciation": "shēn",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "质",
        "back": "matter, material, substance",
        "pronunciation": "zhì",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "价",
        "back": "price, value",
        "pronunciation": "jià",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "整",
        "back": "orderly, neat, tidy; whole",
        "pronunciation": "zhěng",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "况",
        "back": "condition, situation; furthermore",
        "pronunciation": "kuàng",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "亚",
        "back": "Asia; second",
        "pronunciation": "yà",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "技",
        "back": "skill, ability, talent, ingenuity",
        "pronunciation": "jì",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "际",
        "back": "border, boundary, juncture",
        "pronunciation": "jì",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "约",
        "back": "treaty, agreement, covenant",
        "pronunciation": "yuē",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "示",
        "back": "show, manifest; demonstrate",
        "pronunciation": "shì",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "究",
        "back": "examine, investigate",
        "pronunciation": "jiū",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "线",
        "back": "line, thread, wire; clue",
        "pronunciation": "xiàn",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "断",
        "back": "sever, cut off; interrupt",
        "pronunciation": "duàn",
        "collection_id": "4"
    },
    {
        "front": "精",
        "back": "essence; semen; spirit",
        "pronunciation": "jīng",
        "collection_id": "4"
    }
]